Funniest movie you'll ever read.
Casa de Mi Padre is a comedy, western film directed by Matt Piedmont.
Scheming of a way to save their father's ranch, the Alvarez brothers find
themselves in a war with Mexico's most feared drug lord.
Armando Alvarez, played by Will Ferrell.
Esmeralda, played by Mariann Gavelo.
Sheila, played by Molly Shannon.
Onza, played by Gael García Bernal.
Agent Parker, played by Nick Offerman.
Esteban, played by Efren Ramirez.
Casa de mi padre (House of My Father or simply My Father's House) is a 2012 Spanish-language American Western comedy film directed by
Matt Piedmont, written by Harper Steele, and starring Will Ferrell, Gael García Bernal, Diego Luna and Génesis Rodríguez.
It was described to be in the style of an "overly dramatic 1970s telenovela" and tells the story
of Armando Álvarez, who must save his father's ranch from a powerful drug lord.
Casa de mi padre was released on March 16, 2012.
The film explores themes of mexico, organized crime, drug
lord, aftercreditsstinger, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.